letsshave.com 2017-02-24

# Privacy Policy | High Quality Razors and Blades | LetsShave India

This privacy policy sets out how LetsShave.com uses and protects any information that you give when you use this website. 

LetsShave.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. 

LetsShave.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from June 6, 2015. 

**What information do we collect?**  
We collect information from you when you register on the site, place an order, enter a contest or sweepstakes, respond to a survey or communication such as e-mail, or participate in another site feature. When ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. We also collect information about gift recipients so that we can fulfill the gift purchase. The information we collect about gift recipients is not used for marketing purposes. Like many websites, we use "cookies" to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our websites. Please refer to the "Do we use 'cookies'?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them. 

**How do we use your information?**  
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase products, enter a contest or promotion, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways: To personalize your site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested. To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests. To quickly process your transactions. To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature. If you have opted-in to receive our e-mail newsletter, we may send you periodic e-mails. If you would no longer like to receive promotional e-mail from us, please refer to the "How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?" section below. If you have not opted-in to receive e-mail newsletters, you will not receive these e-mails. Visitors who register or participate in other site features such as marketing programs and 'members-only' content will be given a choice whether they would like to be on our e-mail list and receive e-mail communications from us. 

**How do we protect visitor information?**

We are committed to protecting the information we receive from you. We employ strict security measures and management practices to help protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of data stored on our system. We have implemented encryption, SSL, firewalls, and internal restrictions on who may access data to protect our Site and the information we collect from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. The Site uses secure socket layer (SSL) technology to provide for the secure transmission of the information from your personal computer to our servers to encrypt your credit card number/ debit card number, or other payment and personal information. In addition, only those employees and third parties who absolutely need access to your information in order to perform their duties are allowed such access. 

**Do we use "cookies"?**  
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting customer service. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

**Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice, except as described below. The term "outside parties" does not include our business. It also does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

**How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?**  
We provide all users with the opportunity to not to choose receiving non-essential (promotional, marketing-related) communications from us. You have the option to unsubscribe emails if you no longer want to receive e-mail or other communications from LetsShave.com. Please note that due to email production schedules you may receive any emails already in production. Please note that we may maintain information about an individual sales transaction in order to service that transaction and for record keeping. Third party links in an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work). Changes to our policy If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. This policy was last modified on 31st July 2015.

**Links to other websites**  
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information, which you provide whilst visiting such sites and this privacy statement does not govern such sites. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. 

**Controlling your personal information**  
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:  

  * Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
  * If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at [support@letsshave.com]
  * If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect. Please write us at support@letsshave.com

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties, which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. 

**Website Analytics**  
We may use automated applications, such as Google Analytics or other analytic means, to evaluate usage of our website. We use these tools to help us improve our website, performance and user experiences.  

**Changes to this policy  
** We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version will govern our use & reference of your information and will always be available for your review at [www.letsshave.com/privacy-policy](http://www.letsshave.com/privacy-policy). Any changes to this Privacy Policy are subjected without prior notice to you. By continuing to access or use the Services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.  

**Grievance Officer  
** In accordance with Information Technology Act 2000 and rules made there under, the name and contact details of the Grievance Officer who can be contacted with respect to any complaints or concerns or grievances including those pertaining to breach of LetsShave.com’s Terms of Use, and other polices or questions are published as under:  

Grievance Officer Name: Asawari Pawar   
Email address: support@letsshave.com  

**Questions and feedback**  
We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue. Online Policy Only This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

**Your consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
